Art and Architecture of China Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Painting (Box 7)
  - Sung dynasty, 960-1279 (Box 9)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 9)
      - New York (Box 9)
        - Eighteen Songs of a Nomad Flute (Box 9)
        - Evening in Spring Hills (Box 9)
        - Fish and Aquatic Plants (Box 9)
        - Gibbons Attacking Heron Nest (Box 9)
        - Gibbons and Deer (Box 9)
        - Hermitage by Pine-covered Bluff (Box 9)
        - In the Palace (Box 9)
        - Odes of Pin [Slide boxes 53-54] (Box 9)
        - Portrait of Pi Shih-Ch'ang [Slide box 54] (Box 9)
        - River Village in Autumn Dawn (Box 9)
        - Scholars of Liu-li Hall (Box 9)
        - Seeking Shelter (Box 9)
        - Sparrows and Plum Blossoms (Box 9)
        - Tartar Horsemen (Box 9)
        - Travelers in Mountain Landscape (Box 9)
        - Tribute Horse (Box 9)
        - Vimalakirti Sutra (Box 9)
        - Wintry Landscape (Box 9)
      - Peking (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Landscape with People Spinning (Box 9)
        - Landscape with Red Leaf Trees (Box 9)
        - One Hundred Flowers (Box 9)
        - Ox-Carts in Landscape (Box 9)
        - Plowing and Harvesting (Box 9)
        - Travel in Winter (Box 9)
        - Sung-jen Hua-ts'e Album [Slide box 55] (Box 10)
      - Shanghai (Box 10)
        - Various Titles [Slide boxes 55-56] (Box 10)
        - Greeting the Emperor [Slide box 56] (Box 10)
        - Landscape in Kuo His Tradition (Box 10)
        - Sung-jen Hua-miao Album (Box 10)
        - T'ao Hsun Meeting Carriages (Box 10)
        - Travel in Snowy Mountains (Box 10)
      - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
        - Autumn Mountains [Slide box 57] (Box 10)
        - Autumn Trees & White Cloud (Box 10)
        - Bestowing the Peach of Immortality (Box 10)
        - Birds in a Thicket of Bamboo & Prunes (Box 10)
        - Bird on a Camellia Branch (Box 10)
        - Breaking the Balustrade (Box 10)
        - Cat and Peonies (Box 10)
        - Clearing after Snow in the Min Mountains (Box 10)
        - Collating the Text (Box 10)
        - Eighteen Scholars (Box 10)
        - Enjoying the ch'in in a Water Pavilion (Box 10)
        - Enjoying Summer in the Lotus Pavilion (Box 10)
        - Fishing in Seclusion by the Willow Bank (Box 10)
        - Hen & Chickens (Box 10)
        - Joys of Fishing (Box 10)
        - Kitten (Box 10)
        - Listening to the ch'in (Box 10)
        - Market Village by the River (Box 10)
        - Mansion in Wintry Grove (Box 10)
        - Monkeys in a Loquat Tree (Box 10)
        - Noble Scholars under a Willow (Box 10)
        - Old Scholars Meeting (Box 10)
        - Pair of Ducks under Bamboo & Peach Blossoms (Box 10)
        - The Pavilion (Box 10)
        - Peach Blossoms (Box 10)
        - Plucking the Lute (Box 10)
        - Protesting the Seat [Slide box 58] (Box 10)
        - Pure Pleasure under Wu-t'ung Tree (Box 10)
        - Secluded Fishing in a Clear River (Box 10)
        - Small Wintry Grove (Box 10)
        - Snowy Mountains at Dusk (Box 10)
        - Spring Outing (Box 10)
        - Stream-side Conversation (Box 10)
        - Temple on Pine Cliff (Box 10)
        - The Tathagatha Preaching the Law (Box 10)
        - Thousand-Armed Kuan-Yin (Box 10)
        - Turtledoves, Bamboo & Rocks (Box 10)
        - Three Laughs at Hu-Ch'i (Box 10)
      - Washington (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
        - Five Old Men (Box 10)
        - T'ao Yüan-Ming Returning to Seclusion (Box 10)
    - Known Artists (Box 10)
      - Ai Hsuan, 11th century (Box 10)
      - Chang Chi (Box 10)
      - Chang Hsun-Li (Box 10)
      - Chang Kuei (Box 10)
      - Chang Mao, ac. 1190's (Box 10)
      - Chang Sheng-Wen [Slide box 59] (Box 10)
        - Buddhist Images (Box 10)
      - Chang Tse-Tuan, ac. 1100-1150 (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
        - Cities (Box 10)
          - Peking (Box 10)
            - Ch'ing–Ming Festival on the River [Slide boxes 59-60] (Box 10)
      - Chang Tun-Li [Slide box 60] (Box 10)
      - Chang Yu (Box 10)
      - Chang Yueh-Hu (Box 10)
      - Chao Ch'ang, 11th century (Box 10)
      - Chao Ch'iung (Box 10)
      - Chao Kuang-Fu, ac. 960-975 (Box 10)
      - Chao K'uei, 1136-1266 (Box 10)
      - Chao Meng-Chien, 1199-1267 (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
        - Narcissi (Box 10)
      - Chao Po-Chu, ac. c. 1126-1150 [Slide box 61] (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Cities (Box 11)
          - Peking (Box 11)
            - Various Titles (Box 11)
            - Autumn Colors in Rivers & Mountains (Box 11)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 11)
            - Various Titles (Box 11)
            - The Han Palace (Box 11)
            - Spring in the Mountains (Box 11)
      - Chao Po-Su, 12th century (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Landscape with Trees & Birds (Box 11)
        - Reading in the Open Pavilion (Box 11)
      - Chao Shih-Lei (Box 11)
      - Chao Ta-Heng (Box 11)
      - Chao Ta-Nien, ac. c. 1070-1100 (Box 11)
      - Chao Tzu-Hou, 12th century (Box 11)
      - Ch'en Chih-Kung (Box 11)
      - Ch'en Chu-Chung, c. 1205 (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Wen-chi's Return to China (Box 11)
      - Ch'en Jung, c. 1210-1261 [Slide box 62] (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Nine Dragons (Box 11)
      - Ch'i-Chung (Box 11)
      - Ch'i Hsü, 10th century (Box 11)
      - Chia Shih-Ku (Box 11)
      - Chiang Shen. 12th century (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - 1,000 Miles of Rivers & Mountains (Box 11)
        - Verdant Mountains (Box 11)
      - Ch'iao Chung-Ch'ang, 12th century (Box 11)
      - Chih-weng (Box 11)
      - Chin Ta-Shou, 12th century (Box 11)
      - Chou Chi-Ch'ang, 12th century (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Cities (Box 11)
          - Boston (Box 11)
          - Washington [Slide box 63] (Box 11)
      - Chu-Jan, c. 980 (Box 11)
        - Cities (Box 11)
          - Various Titles (Box 11)
          - Cleveland (Box 11)
          - Shanghai (Box 11)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 11)
            - Various Titles (Box 11)
            - Asking about the Tao in Autumn Mountains (Box 11)
            - Autumn Mountains (Box 11)
            - Distant Mountain Forest (Box 11)
            - Hsiao I Seizing the Lan-T'ing (Box 11)
            - Pine Cliffs & Temples (Box 11)
            - Snow Landscape (Box 11)
      - Chu Jui, ac. c. end of 12th century (Box 11)
      - Chu Kuang-P'u (Box 11)
      - Ch'u Ting, ac. 11th century (Box 11)
      - Chu Tz'u-Chung [Slide box 64] (Box 11)
      - Fan K'uan, 950-1026 (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Sitting Alone by a Stream (Box 11)
        - Travelers among Mountains & Streams (Box 11)
      - Fan-Lung (Box 11)
      - Feng Ta-Yu (Box 11)
      - Han Yu (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Cities [Slide box 65] (Box 11)
          - Kansas City (Box 11)
          - New York (Box 11)
          - Peking (Box 11)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 11)
            - Various Titles (Box 11)
            - Pure & Remote View of Stream & Mills (Box 11)
            - Ten Thousand Miles of Yangtze River (Box 11)
      - Hsia Sheng (Box 11)
      - Hsiao Chao, 12th century (Box 11)
      - Hsü Tao-Ning, c. 1000-1050 (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Cities (Box 11)
          - Kansas City (Box 11)
            - Fishing in a Mountain Stream [Slide boxes 65-66] (Box 11)
          - Kyoto [Slide box 66] (Box 11)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 11)
            - Fishing on a Snowy River (Box 11)
            - Heavy Snow on a Mountain Pass (Box 11)
      - Hu Chih-Fu (Box 11)
      - Hu Shun-Ch'en, ac. early 12th century (Box 11)
        - Huang Chu-Ts'ai (Box 11)
      - Hui Ch'ung (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Mandarin Ducks under Winter Trees (Box 11)
      - Hui Tsung, 1082-1126 (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Cities (Box 11)
          - Boston (Box 11)
            - Parakeet (Box 11)
            - Ladies Preparing Silk [Slide box 67] (Box 12)
          - New York (Box 12)
          - Peking (Box 12)
          - Shenyang (Box 12)
            - Rowing Home on a Snowy River (Box 12)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 12)
            - Various Titles (Box 12)
            - Autumn over Hills & River (Box 12)
            - A Literary Gathering (Box 12)
            - The Pond's Edge in Late Autumn (Box 12)
            - Two Bulbuls on a Flowering Allspice (Box 12)
      - I Yüan-Chi, d. 1066 (Box 12)
      - Kao K'o-Ming, c. 1008-1053 (Box 12)
      - Kao Tao (Box 12)
      - Kao-Tsung [Slide box 68] (Box 12)
      - Kung K'ai, 13th century (Box 12)
      - Kuo Hsi, c. 1020-1090 (Box 12)
        - Various Titles (Box 12)
        - Cities (Box 12)
          - New York (Box 12)
            - Trees on a Low Plain (Box 12)
          - Shanghai (Box 12)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 12)
            - Various Titles (Box 12)
            - Early Spring (Box 12)
          - Toledo (Box 12)
          - Washington [Slide box 69] (Box 12)
            - Clearing Autumn Skies over Mountains & Valleys (Box 12)
      - Li of Shu-ch'eng (Box 12)
        - Li Ch'eng, c. 916-967 (Box 12)
          - Various Titles (Box 12)
          - Cities (Box 12)
            - Boston (Box 12)
            - Kansas City (Box 12)
              - Buddhist Temple Amid Clearing in Mountain Skies (Box 12)
            - Liaoning (Box 12)
              - Mao-lin Yuan-hsiu T'u (Box 12)
              - Wintry Forest (Box 12)
            - New York [Slide box 70] (Box 12)
              - Travelers in a Winter Forest (Box 12)
            - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 12)
              - Various Titles (Box 12)
              - Fishing on a Wintry River (Box 12)
      - Li An-Chung, 1120-1160 (Box 12)
      - Li Chin (Box 12)
      - Li Ch'ueh (Box 12)
      - Li Kung-Lin, c. 1040-1106 (Box 12)
        - Various Titles (Box 12)
        - An Assembly of Immortals (Box 12)
        - Dwelling in the Lung-Mien Mountains (Box 12)
        - Five Horses (Box 12)
          - Cities (Box 12)
            - Peking (Box 12)
              - One Hundred Horses (Box 12)
              - Illustration of the Classic of Filial Piety [Slide boxes 70-71] (Box 12)
            - Taipei (Taichung) [Slide box 71] (Box 12)
              - Kuo Tzu-I Receiving Homage of the Uigurs (Box 12)
              - Mountain Retreat (Box 12)
      - Li Kung-Nien, ac. c. 1100 (Box 12)
        - Cities (Box 12)
          - Princeton (Box 12)
        - Li Shan (Box 12)
          - Various Titles (Box 12)
          - Wind and Snow in the Fir Trees (Box 12)
      - Li Sung, c. 1160-1240 (Box 12)
        - Various Titles (Box 12)
        - Cities (Box 12)
          - Peking (Box 12)
            - Various Titles (Box 12)
            - Skeleton Puppet Master (Box 12)
          - Shanghai [Slide box 72] (Box 12)
            - West Lake (Box 12)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 12)
            - Various Titles (Box 12)
            - Knick-Knack Peddler (Box 12)
            - Listening to the Yuan (Box 12)
            - Sleeping in the Pine Breeze (Box 12)
            - The Flower Basket (Box 12)
            - The Hangchow bore in Moonlight (Box 12)
      - Li T'ang, c. 1050-1130 (Box 12)
        - Cities (Box 12)
          - Various Titles (Box 12)
          - Kyoto (Box 12)
          - New York (Box 12)
            - Marquis Wen-Kung of Chin Recovering His State (Box 12)
          - Peking [Slide box 73] (Box 13)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 13)
            - Various Titles (Box 13)
            - Landscapes of the Four Seasons (Box 13)
            - Mountains by the River (Box 13)
            - Wen Chi's Return to China (Box 13)
            - Whispering Pines in the Mountains (Box 13)
      - Li Ti, c. 1100-1197 (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
        - Cities (Box 13)
          - Various Titles (Box 13)
          - Cleveland (Box 13)
          - Peking [Slide box 74] (Box 13)
          - Shanghai (Box 13)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 13)
            - Various Titles (Box 13)
            - Scholar of the Eastern Fence (Box 13)
          - Tokyo (Box 13)
            - Various Titles (Box 13)
            - Snow Landscape (Box 13)
      - Liang Shih-Min, ac. 12th century (Box 13)
      - Lien Fu (Box 13)
      - Lin Ch'un, ac. c. 1175-1200 (Box 13)
        - Cities (Box 13)
          - Various Titles (Box 13)
          - Peking (Box 13)
          - Taipei (Taichung) [Slide box 75] (Box 13)
      - Liu Sung-Nien, ac. 1195-1224 (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
        - Cities (Box 13)
          - Peking (Box 13)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 13)
            - Various Titles (Box 13)
            - Lohans (Box 13)
            - Scholars (Box 13)
              - Five Scholars of the T'ang Dynasty (Box 13)
              - Eighteen Scholars (Box 13)
      - Liu Tsai, 11th century (Box 13)
      - Liu Yung-Nien, c. 1020 (Box 13)
      - Lo Ch'uang, 13th century (Box 13)
      - Lou Kuan, 13th century (Box 13)
      - Lu Hsin-Chung (Box 13)
      - Lu Tsung-Kuei, 13th century (Box 13)
      - Ma Fen [Slide box 76] (Box 13)
        - The Hundred Geese (Box 13)
      - Ma Ho-Chih, c. 1130-1180 (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
        - Cities (Box 13)
          - Boston (Box 13)
          - New York (Box 13)
            - Various Titles (Box 13)
            - Odes of the State of Pin (Box 13)
          - Peking (Box 13)
          - Taipei (Taichung) [Slide box 77] (Box 13)
            - Various Titles (Box 13)
            - The Book of Filial Piety (Box 13)
            - Ladies' Hsiao-Ching (Box 13)
      - Ma K'uei, c. 1150-1224 (Box 13)
      - Ma Kung-Hsien (Box 13)
      - Ma Lin, c. 1190-1260 (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
        - Cities (Box 13)
          - Cleveland (Box 13)
          - New York (Box 13)
          - Peking (Box 13)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 13)
            - Various Titles (Box 13)
            - Dark Fragrances and Scattered Shadows (Box 13)
            - Fragrant Spring (Box 13)
            - Listening to the Wind in the Pines (Box 13)
            - Waiting for Guests by Lamplight [Slide box 78] (Box 13)
      - Ma Yüan, c. 1190-1224 (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
        - 10-Leaf Album with Poems by Empress Yang (Box 13)
        - Cities (Box 13)
          - Various Titles (Box 13)
          - Boston (Box 13)
          - Cleveland (Box 13)
          - Kansas City (Box 13)
            - Elegant Gathering in the Western Garden (Box 13)
          - Peking [Slide box 79] (Box 14)
            - Various Titles (Box 14)
            - Peasants Dancing (Box 14)
            - Water (Box 14)
          - Suchow (Box 14)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 14)
            - Various Titles (Box 14)
            - Apricot Blossoms (Box 14)
            - Banquet by Lantern Light (Box 14)
            - Collection of Small Pictures (Box 14)
            - Landscape & Figures (Box 14)
            - On a Mountain Path in Spring (Box 14)
            - Playing the Lute in Moonlight (Box 14)
            - Snow Landscapes (Box 14)
            - Through Snowy Mountains at Dawn (Box 14)
            - Two Birds at the Pine Spring (Box 14)
          - Tokyo (Box 14)
      - Mao I, ac. 1165-1173 (Box 14)
      - Mao Sung (Box 14)
      - Mi Fei (Mi Fu) [Slide box 80] (Box 14)
      - Mi Yu-Jen, 1086-1165 (Box 14)
        - Various Titles (Box 14)
        - Cities (Box 14)
          - Cleveland (Box 14)
          - Shanghai (Box 14)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 14)
      - Mou Chung-Fu (Box 14)
      - Mou I (Box 14)
        - Clothes for the Warriors (Box 14)
      - Mu Ch'i (Box 14)
        - Various Titles (Box 14)
        - Cities (Box 14)
          - Cleveland (Box 14)
          - Kyoto (Box 14)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 14)
          - Tokyo [Slide box 81] (Box 14)
      - Pi Lang-Shih (Box 14)
      - P'u An (Box 14)
      - P'u Yüeh, 12th century (Box 14)
      - Su Han-Ch'en, ac. c. 1101-1163 (Box 14)
      - Su Shih, 1036-1101 (Box 14)
      - Sun Chih-Wei, ac. a. 1000 (Box 14)
      - Sung Ju-Chih (Box 14)
      - Sung Ti, 11th century (Box 14)
      - Sung-T'ien, 13th century (Box 14)
      - Tsui Ch'üeh, 2nd half of 11th century (Box 14)
      - Ts'ui Po, 11th century (Box 14)
      - Wang Chu-Cheng, ac. 11th century [Slide box 82] (Box 14)
      - Wang Hsi-Meng, ac. 1119-1125 (Box 14)
      - Wang Hung, c. 1150 (Box 14)
      - Wang Li-Yung (Box 14)
      - Wang Ning, 11th century (Box 14)
      - Wang Shen, c. 1050-1100 (Box 14)
        - Various Titles (Box 14)
        - Cities (Box 14)
          - Shanghai (Box 14)
            - Serried Peaks by a Misty River (Box 14)
            - Light Snow on a Fishing Village (Box 14)
          - Taipei (Box 14)
            - Various Titles (Box 14)
            - Isles of the Immortals (Box 14)
      - Wang Qihan, ac.c. 961-975 (Box 14)
      - Wang T'ing-yän, 1151-1202 (Box 14)
      - Wang Yen-Sou (Box 14)
      - Wei Sheng (Box 14)
      - Wen T'ung, 1049-1079 [Slide box 83] (Box 14)
      - Wu Ping (Box 14)
        - Various Titles (Box 14)
        - Cities (Box 14)
          - Cleveland (Box 14)
          - Peking (Box 14)
      - Wu Shu-Ming (Box 14)
      - Wu Tsung-Yüan (Box 14)
      - Wu Yüan-Chih (Box 14)
      - Yang Pu-Chih, 1097-1169 (Box 14)
      - Yang Shih-Hsien (Box 14)
      - Yang Wu-Chiu, 1097-1171 (Box 14)
      - Yeh Hsiao-Yen (Box 14)
      - Yen Chih-Chih, 13th century (Box 14)
      - Yen Tz'u–P'ing, ac. C. 1165-1181 (Box 14)
        - Various Titles (Box 14)
        - Cities (Box 14)
          - Suchow (Box 14)
            - Buffaloes (Box 14)
          - Taipei (Box 14)
            - The Four Pleasures (Box 14)
            - Rowing Home over Mirror Lake (Box 14)
            - Villa by the Pine Path (Box 14)
      - Yen Tz'u-Yü (Box 14)
      - Yen Wen-Kuei, 967-1044 (Box 14)
        - Various Titles (Box 14)
        - Cities (Box 14)
          - Osaka [Slide boxes 83-84] (Box 14)
          - Taipei [Slide box 84] (Box 14)
            - Various Titles (Box 14)
            - Mountain Stream and Temples (Box 14)
          - Tokyo (Box 14)
      - Ying Yü-Chien, 13th century (Box 14)
      - Yu Chien, 13th century (Box 14)
  - Yüan dynasty, 1260-1368 (Box 14)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 14)
      - Various Titles (Box 14)
      - Chicago (Box 14)
      - Cleveland (Box 14)
      - Kansas City [Slide boxes 84-85] (Box 14–15)
      - Kyoto [Slide box 85] (Box 15)
      - Liaoning (Box 15)
      - New York (Box 15)
        - Various Titles (Box 15)
        - Su Shih's Ode (Box 15)
      - Peking (Box 15)
        - Various Titles (Box 15)
        - Dragon Boat Festival (Box 15)
        - Villa in Mountains (Box 15)
      - Suchow (Box 15)
      - Taipei [Slide boxes 85-86] (Box 15)
      - Tokyo [Slide box 86] (Box 15)
      - Washington (Box 15)
    - Known Artists (Box 15)
      - Ch'ai Chen, ac. c. 1349 (Box 15)
      - Chang Chung, ac. c. 1336-1360 (Box 15)
      - Chang Hsun (Box 15)
      - Chang Kuan, a. mid-14th century (Box 15)
      - Chang Shou-Chung, a. mid-14th century (Box 15)
      - Chang Shun-Tzu, ac. 1330-1350 (Box 15)
      - Chang Wu, ac. 1335-1365 (Box 15)
        - The Nine Songs (Box 15)
      - Chang Yen-Fu, 14th century (Box 15)
      - Chang Yu-Ts'ai, d. 1316 (Box 15)
      - Chang Yuan (Box 15)
      - Chao Chung, 14th century (Box 15)
      - Chao Lin, 14th century (Box 15)
      - Chan Lingjang (Zhao Lingrang) (Box 15)
      - Chao Meng-Fu, 1254-1322 [Slide box 87] (Box 15)
        - Various Titles (Box 15)
        - Cities (Box 15)
          - Cincinnati (Box 15)
          - Cleveland (Box 15)
          - New York (Box 15)
            - Various Titles (Box 15)
            - Old Tree, Bamboo & Rock (Box 15)
            - Twin Pines & Level Distance (Box 15)
          - Peking (Box 15)
            - Various Titles (Box 15)
            - Red-Coated Official on Horseback (Box 15)
            - Washing Horses (Box 15)
            - Water Village (Box 15)
          - Shanghai (Box 15)
            - Various Titles (Box 15)
            - Tung-Shan [Slide box 88] (Box 15)
          - Taipei (Box 15)
            - Autumn Colors (Box 15)
            - Hsiao-Ching (Box 15)
            - Ink Bamboo & Rock (Box 15)
            - Rivers & Peaks (Box 15)
          - Washington (Box 15)
            - Various Titles (Box 15)
            - A Goat & A Sheep (Box 15)
      - Chao Meng-Fu, copy after (Box 15)
        - Nine Songs [Slide boxes 88-89] (Box 15)
      - Chao Yüan, ac. c. 1370 [Slide box 89] (Box 15)
        - Various Titles (Box 15)
        - Cities (Box 15)
          - New York (Box 15)
            - Various Titles (Box 15)
            - Farewell by a Stream on a Clear Day (Box 15)
            - Taipei (Box 15)
      - Chao Yung, b. 1289 (Box 15)
        - Various Titles (Box 15)
        - Cities (Box 15)
          - Cleveland (Box 15)
          - Peking (Box 15)
          - Taipei (Box 15)
            - Various Titles (Box 15)
            - Boating in the Mountains (Box 15)
            - Gathering Water Chestnuts (Box 15)
            - The Noble Steeds (Box 15)
      - Ch'en Ju-Yen, ac. 1340-1380 (Box 15)
        - Various Titles (Box 15)
        - Cities (Box 15)
          - Cleveland (Box 15)
            - Land of the Immortals (Box 15)
            - Lo-Fou-Shan's Woodcutter (Box 15)
      - Ch'en Li-Shan, ac. c. 1350 (Box 15)
      - Ch'en Lin, ac. c. 1300 [Slide box 90] (Box 15)
      - Cheng Hsi, ac. c. 1350 (Box 15)
      - Cheng Ssu-Hsiao, 1238-1315 (Box 15)
      - Ch'ien Hsüan, 1235-c. 1300 (Box 15)
        - Various Titles (Box 15)
        - Cities (Box 15)
          - Detroit (Box 15)
          - New York (Box 15)
          - Peking (Box 15)
          - Shanghai (Box 15)
          - Taipei (Box 15)
            - Taipei Various Titles (Box 15)
            - Autumn Melon (Box 15)
            - Squirrel on a Peach Branch (Box 15)
            - Waiting for the Ferry at the Misty River (Box 15)
            - Watching the Geese at Lan-T'ing (Box 15)
          - Washington (Box 15)
      - Chou Tung'Ch'ing, 13th century [Slide box 91] (Box 16)
      - Chu Shu-Chung, ac. c. 1365 (Box 16)
      - Chu Te-Jun, 1294-1365 (Box 16)
        - Cities (Box 16)
          - Various Titles (Box 16)
          - Peking (Box 16)
      - Chuang Lin (Box 16)
      - Chueh-Chi Yung-Cheng (Box 16)
      - Fang Ts'ung-I, ac. c. 1365 (Box 16)
      - Fang Yai, ac. c. 1360 (Box 16)
      - Ho Ch'eng, c. 1224-1316 (Box 16)
      - Hsia Shu-Wen (Box 16)
      - Hsia Yung, 14th century (?) (Box 16)
      - Hsieh P'o-Ch'eng, ac. 14th century (Box 16)
      - Hsu-Chou P'u-Tu (Box 16)
      - Hu T'ing-Hui, ac.c. 1300 (Box 16)
      - Huang Kung-Wang, 1269-1354 (Box 16)
        - Cities (Box 16)
          - Various Titles (Box 16)
          - Hangchow (Box 16)
            - Landscape: Fu-Ch'un Fragment [Slide boxes 91-92] (Box 16)
          - Nanking [Slide box 92] (Box 16)
            - Fu-Ch'un Ta-Ling T'u (Box 16)
            - Shan-Chu T'u (Box 16)
          - Peking (Box 16)
            - Nine Peaked Mountain after Snow (Box 16)
            - T'ien-Ch'ih Shih-Pi T'u (Box 16)
            - Yü-I-T'u (Box 16)
          - Taipei (Box 16)
            - Various (Box 16)
            - Dwelling in the Fu-Ch'un Mountains (Box 16)
      - I-An, ac.c. 1300 (?) (Box 16)
      - Jen Jen-Fa, 1255-1328 (See also Ren Renfa) (Box 16)
        - Various Titles (Box 16)
        - Cities (Box 16)
          - Cleveland (Box 16)
          - Kansas City [Slide box 93] (Box 16)
          - Peking (Box 16)
            - Various Titles (Box 16)
            - The Lean Horse & The Fat Horse (Box 16)
            - Chang Kuo-Lao (Box 16)
      - Kao K'o-Kung, 1248-1310 (Box 16)